<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Characterbios on Z-R1Nzoe&#39;s den</title>
    <link>/characterbios/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Characterbios on Z-R1Nzoe&#39;s den</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 22:30:31 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/characterbios/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Maezie&#39;s Bio</title>
      <link>/characterbios/maeziebio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 22:30:31 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/characterbios/maeziebio/</guid>
      <description>Maezie Delilah Rosse About
Appearance
Abilities
Gear &amp;amp; Weapons
Midnight Sonata
Dual Viperions
Assault Boots
Relationships
Reference Images
Gallery
Trivia
Catergories Details Nicknames Mae, mae-mae Species Cat (Maine Coon/Bombay mix) Age Young adult (&amp;gt;18) Gender Female Pronouns She/Her &amp;amp; They/Them Sexuality AroAce DOB 13th April Marital Status Single Place of Birth ??? Residence New Tymes City Key abilities Energy Manipulation, Peak feline abilities, Broadsword Proficiensy About: Maezie Delilah Rossi, or just Maezie, is a Feline Vigilante living in New Tymes City.</description>
      <content>&lt;h1 id=&#34;umaezie-delilah-rosseu&#34;&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maezie Delilah Rosse&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;images/maezieref.png&#34;  alt=&#34;Maezie ref&#34;  class=&#34;left&#34;  style=&#34;float:right&#34;   width=&#34;500px&#34;   /&gt;


&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#about&#34;&gt;About&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#appearance&#34;&gt;Appearance&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#abilities&#34;&gt;Abilities&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#gear%20&amp;amp;%20weapons&#34;&gt;Gear &amp;amp; Weapons&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#midnight%20sonata&#34;&gt;Midnight Sonata&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#dual%20hyperions&#34;&gt;Dual Viperions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#assault%20boots&#34;&gt;Assault Boots&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#relationships&#34;&gt;Relationships&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#reference%20images&#34;&gt;Reference Images&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#gallery&#34;&gt;Gallery&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#trivia&#34;&gt;Trivia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Catergories&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Details&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Nicknames&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Mae, mae-mae&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Species&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Cat (Maine Coon/Bombay mix)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Age&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Young adult (&amp;gt;18)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Gender&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Female&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Pronouns&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;She/Her &amp;amp; They/Them&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Sexuality&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;AroAce&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;DOB&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;13th April&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Marital Status&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Single&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Place of Birth&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;???&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Residence&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;New Tymes City&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Key abilities&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Energy Manipulation, Peak feline abilities, Broadsword Proficiensy&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;about&#34;&gt;About:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maezie Delilah Rossi, or just Maezie, is a Feline Vigilante living in New Tymes City. Using her alias of &amp;ldquo;Z-lyn3&amp;rdquo;, she fights against the dark criminal underbelly of the city, as well as fighting against the corrupt corporations that seek to turn the city into their own personal capitalist hellscape&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;appearance&#34;&gt;Appearance:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maezie has a small and slender frame, with a mostly hourglass shaped body adorned with short, dark grey-ish black fur, as well as a similarly coloured tail. Her hair is short and messy green, with slightly longer hair on the back of her head. Her nose, as well as the tips of her fingers, the inside of her ears and her nipples all possess light pink skin. In terms of attire, the most common throughline is some form of spiked bracelet and collar, usually a black one with short spikes if she is in sleeping attire, but usually wears more spiked clothing when she is out and about. (Section is temporarily unfinished due to upcoming outfit changes)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;character&#34;&gt;Character:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maezie is not one to quickly open up her feelings, due to past rejections and her own personal issues, usually resulting in her keeping to herself especially on missions. However, to those who she is familiar with, she&amp;rsquo;s far more eccentric and outgoing, easily making jokes with her fellow teammates and friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;abilities&#34;&gt;Abilities:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Due to an incident that Maezie has seemingly no memory off, she is capable of manipulating different forms of energy; The main forms of energy she is known to manipulate are kinetic energy, electrical energy, thermal energy and radioactive energy. As a result of this ability, maezie is capable of manipulating the strength of her attacks by increasing the kinetic energy they have, as well as being able to apply freezing cold or burning hot temperatures to them, as well as low level control over fire and ice. She is also capable of controlling electricity, and is immune to radiation. However, a key drawback to her abilities is that prolonged usage of her abilities can cause damage to her body, with more excessive usage potentially leading to permanent or even fatal damage. The only ability exempt from this is the radiation immunity, an ability that is permanently active at a low level. Gear like the Assault Boots and the Battle Gauntlets do mitigate some of the downsides, but it&amp;rsquo;s not a permanent solution. Only Thorough training and getting used to her powers will allow Maezie to use her powers to their full extent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Outside of her abilities, she also is very physically and mentally adept, due to training from a fairly young age. As a result of this, she is capable of performing feats that far exceed the capabilities of a normal feline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;gear--weapons&#34;&gt;Gear &amp;amp; Weapons:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both in the real world and in cyberspace, Maezie has an extensive amount of gear and weapons at her disposal, as well as different upgrades to said gear and weapons, making Maezie into a very versatile combatant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;weapons&#34;&gt;Weapons:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;moonlight-sonata&#34;&gt;Moonlight Sonata:&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite it&amp;rsquo;s macabre name, the Moonlight Sonata is a powerful photon broadsword, built out of the supposed remains of the legendary sword Caledfwlch. The sword is seemingly the only weapon in Maezie&amp;rsquo;s arsenal that can transcend the physical world, following her into cyberspace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;dual-viperions&#34;&gt;Dual Viperions:&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Dual Viperions, a pair of black and neon green energy pistols, modified from a pre-existing energy pistol model to suit maezie to feature a modular system. Due to it being modular, it can be modified to suit multiple different scenarios.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;gear&#34;&gt;Gear:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;assault-boots&#34;&gt;Assault Boots&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The assault boots, also known as the &amp;ldquo;Assisted Surface Scaling and Utility Traversal Boots&amp;rdquo;, or the &amp;ldquo;big stompers&amp;rdquo; by Maezie, are a pair of highly advanced cybernetic boots, which take the form of black studded platform boots. The boots allow the user to not only kick off of walls to gain altitude, but also allow the user to perform an in-air jump due to a series of null-gravity repulsors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;battle-gauntlets&#34;&gt;Battle Gauntlets:&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Battle Gauntlets, much like the Assault boots, are a pair of highly advanced cybernetic gloves, which take the form of a pair of black fingerless gloves with spikes around the wrist. The wrist allow for better control of Maezie&amp;rsquo;s energy manipulation, as well as having a built-in PDA to allow maezie to keep track of vigilante tasks, as well as functioning like a smart watch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;vented-face-mask&#34;&gt;Vented Face-Mask&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The vented face mask, as the name would imply, is a face mask designed to cover up Maezie&amp;rsquo;s mouth and nose. While stylized like a digital pair of jaws, the face mask allows for the filtration of toxins and smoke from the air, as well as concealing Maezie&amp;rsquo;s identity by hiding her face and modulating her voice (the voice modulation is usually disabled by Maezie&amp;rsquo;s choice).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;relationships&#34;&gt;Relationships&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;STILL IN DEVELOPMENT&amp;lt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;reference-images&#34;&gt;Reference Images&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;STILL IN DEVELOPMENT&amp;lt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;gallery&#34;&gt;Gallery&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;STILL IN DEVELOPMENT&amp;lt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;trivia&#34;&gt;Trivia&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Her Assault boots, albeit more based on the appearance of goth/emo platform boots, are actually based off of the Sun Greaves from the indie game Pseudoregalia, especially in how both the Sun Greaves and the Assault Boots allow Sybil and Maezie respectively to perform in-air kicks and wall kicks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Her favorite food is Oven-Cooked chicken wings, with her favorite ones being from a small restaurant/pub called &amp;ldquo;The Drunken Maiden&amp;rdquo;, where the wings in question are cooked with a crispy skin, succulent meat underneath, and sauced in a fruity and sweet but spicy sauce, served alongside a portion of chips with ranch dressing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Riesha&#39;s Bio</title>
      <link>/characterbios/rikkabio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 22:30:31 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/characterbios/rikkabio/</guid>
      <description>Riesha Selene Corpus About
Appearance
Abilities
Gear &amp;amp; Weapons
Relationships
Reference Images
Gallery
Trivia
Catergories Details Nicknames RiRi, Enchantress of the damned Species Wolf (Undead) Age Young Adult Gender Cis-Female Pronouns She/Her &amp;amp; They/Them Sexuality Bisexual DOB 30th october Marital Status Single Place of Birth Cradlewood, allington Residence Cradlewood Manor Key abilities Magic (Necromancy, Biomancy, Pyromancy, Cryomancy), Undead physiology About: Riesha Corpus, Or usually just Ri, is an undead wolf witch; The daughter of an infamous yokai, known to prey on newly wed men and unfaithful boyfriends, and a high ranking hellhound, Riesha is both a very powerful and very capable person, if she wasn&amp;rsquo;t also a hikikomori.</description>
      <content>&lt;h1 id=&#34;uriesha-selene-corpusu&#34;&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Riesha Selene Corpus&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;images/Rieshapic.png&#34;  alt=&#34;Riesha Pic&#34;  class=&#34;left&#34;  style=&#34;float:right&#34;   width=&#34;500px&#34;   /&gt;


&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#about&#34;&gt;About&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#appearance&#34;&gt;Appearance&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#abilities&#34;&gt;Abilities&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#gear%20&amp;amp;%20weapons&#34;&gt;Gear &amp;amp; Weapons&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#relationships&#34;&gt;Relationships&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#reference%20images&#34;&gt;Reference Images&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#gallery&#34;&gt;Gallery&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#trivia&#34;&gt;Trivia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Catergories&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Details&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Nicknames&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;RiRi, Enchantress of the damned&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Species&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Wolf (Undead)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Age&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Young Adult&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Gender&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Cis-Female&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Pronouns&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;She/Her &amp;amp; They/Them&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Sexuality&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Bisexual&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;DOB&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;30th october&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Marital Status&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Single&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Place of Birth&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Cradlewood, allington&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Residence&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Cradlewood Manor&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Key abilities&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Magic (Necromancy, Biomancy, Pyromancy, Cryomancy), Undead physiology&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;about&#34;&gt;About:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Riesha Corpus, Or usually just Ri, is an undead wolf witch; The daughter of an infamous yokai, known to prey on newly wed men and unfaithful boyfriends, and a high ranking hellhound, Riesha is both a very powerful and very capable person, if she wasn&amp;rsquo;t also a hikikomori.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a while, she was the main antagonist for a children&amp;rsquo;s edutainment series &amp;ldquo;Ruby&amp;rsquo;s World&amp;rdquo;, but after a few seasons, a straight to DVD movie and a computer game too advanced for the time, the series was discontinued and fell into obscurity, save for a small niché fandom that remember the series.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After that time, Riesha spent most of her time stuck indoors, due to social anxiety stemming from her treatment in Ruby&amp;rsquo;s World, leading to her status as a hikikomori.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;appearance-and-characteristics&#34;&gt;Appearance and Characteristics:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Designwise, Riesha has Feldgrau coloured fur (#4D685A), with the exception of her lower right leg and left arm, which is more of an oxford blue colour (#0A2342), as well as having long messy orange hair (#F58F29) and Raspberry rose coloured eyes (#A53860) with black sclera. She has a very slim and slender physique, with notable stich marks on her body, as well as her lower ribs being exposed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For her basic attire, she wears a pair of black high heeled boots, with orange striping going across them, as well as black stockings and a slightly oversized black shirt. She also wears a pair of black bracelets with orange gemstones adorning them, as well as a collar with a large central orange gemstone and a large witch&amp;rsquo;s hat, adorned with the similar gemstones and a long tassel that forms into a large clawed hand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;personality&#34;&gt;Personality:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Riesha, at first glance, is very much a tone deaf character, being very blunt with people even if it such bluntness could mean angering the person she is speaking to. She is also somewhat of a trickster, her abilities and her sharp tongue being major tools in angering and baiting those she has taken a fancy to into a disadvantageous position. However, with those she is comfortable with, she tries her best to hold her sharp tongue, and generally cares more about their feelings. While she may be a trickster witch, she very much cares for people and is willing to do what she can to help others, even if the means of doing so aren&amp;rsquo;t what many people would consider conventional.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;abilities--techniques&#34;&gt;Abilities &amp;amp; Techniques:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;uabilitiesu&#34;&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;Abilities:&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;magic&#34;&gt;Magic:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When it comes to the arcane arts, Riesha is one of the most powerful sorcerers in her world, being able to conjure very advanced spells with relative ease, and being able to cast basic spells as easily as reading words from a book. Her magical potential stems from her unorthodox method of focusing arcane energy, as the gaping tear in her chest is, in fact, her arcane focus. She also uses the souls of those who have wronged her, trapped inside her very chest, as boosters for her arcane abilities. Her most prominent form of magic is that of necromancy, complimenting her undead disposition; She is very capable of summoning hordes of the undead with merely a flick of her wrist, and can easily convert those who have fallen by her hands into necrotic thralls. She is also skilled in biomancy, an offshoot form from necromancy that uses flesh, bone and bile to create constructs, perform attacks or to augment herself. Besides these, she is also skilled in other elemental forms of magic, such as pyromantic magic and geomancy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;undead-physiology&#34;&gt;Undead Physiology:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Due to the nature of being an undead being, Riesha gains many benefits; Firstly, she is completely immune to diseases, as her body is already dead meaning there is nothing for diseases to even infect. Secondly, she is able to recover from injuries fairly quickly, either by using her own biomancy to repair her body, or using the body parts of other corpses to repair damage done to her body. However, there is some caveats to her undead state; One key downside is that she does have a craving for the flesh of living beings. While she can mitigate this by consuming normal meat frequently and then dining on a pound of flesh from a sentient being once a month, ignoring this need can lead to her body failing to regenerate decaying flesh, as well as her mind becoming more feral. Another caveat is, due to her decaying state and her exposed chest tear, she is easily considered to many to be unsettling, as she is a literal walking corpse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;power-replication&#34;&gt;Power Replication:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While linked to her &amp;ldquo;Soul Equalizer&amp;rdquo; technique, Riesha is able to gain the power and relative strength of those she has chosen to mimic. She can use this to replicate the strengths of her opponents, as well as any unique traits that they may have. One key downside to this technique, outside of the setup time needed to perform the technique, is that it does not copy the target&amp;rsquo;s proficiency in said abilities, nor their resistances to said abilities. For example, if a power her target has requires a significant stamina draw, but the target already has gotten used to the draw, Riesha would still have to content to the stamina draw.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;utechniquesu&#34;&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;Techniques&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;bile-ball&#34;&gt;Bile Ball:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Riesha users her arcane energy to form a fleshy mass in the form of a ball, which she throws at an opponent. Once it collides with an opponent, it explodes, releasing the stored bile inside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;arcane-bouncer&#34;&gt;Arcane Bouncer:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Riesha, using the controllable tassel on her witch&amp;rsquo;s hat (or a fleshy claw tendril, if she doesn&amp;rsquo;t have her hat), forms a ball of arcane energy, which she throws at her opponent. The arcane energy is capable of ricocheting off of surfaces, and can be detonated upon command.Rieshaa can also use the Arcane bouncer as a form of transport, allowing her to speed across distances at high speeds&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;soul-equalizer&#34;&gt;Soul Equalizer:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Riesha uses her arcane energy to replicate her target&amp;rsquo;s powers and relative strength. While she can augment said powers with her own abilities, she does still have to content with the downsides of the powers that she replicates. She also does not replicate the target&amp;rsquo;s battle proficiency&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NOTE: The below techniques are considered NON-CANON, and are purely made for fan service reasons&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;gear--weapons&#34;&gt;Gear &amp;amp; Weapons:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;uweaponsu&#34;&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;Weapons:&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;ugearu&#34;&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;Gear:&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;relationships&#34;&gt;Relationships&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;family&#34;&gt;Family:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;allies&#34;&gt;Allies:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;enemies&#34;&gt;Enemies:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;reference-images&#34;&gt;Reference Images&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;STILL IN DEVELOPMENT&amp;lt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;gallery&#34;&gt;Gallery&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;STILL IN DEVELOPMENT&amp;lt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;extra-detailstrivia&#34;&gt;Extra Details/Trivia&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;While she is female presenting, she does speak with a somewhat deeper voice [Think the sort of voice that Nancy has from Necro Nancy].&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;While she is a reanimated corpse, she is not a zombie as she does not need to consume flesh&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;authors-notes&#34;&gt;Author&amp;rsquo;s notes:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zoe&#39;s Bio</title>
      <link>/characterbios/zoebio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 22:30:31 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/characterbios/zoebio/</guid>
      <description>Empress Zoe Crosse About
Appearance
Abilities
Gear &amp;amp; Weapons
Relationships
Reference Images
Gallery
Trivia
Catergories Details Nicknames Zo-Zo, Crimson Empress Species Dragon (Ancient Earth/Fire Dragon mix Age Adult (~27 physically, 1000+ actually) Gender Trans-Female Pronouns She/Her &amp;amp; They/Them Sexuality AroAce DOB 30th june Marital Status Single Place of Birth ??? Residence Draco Syndicate Base, New Draconya Key abilities Antimatter manipulation, Conditional Immortality, Elemental Control, Mind control About: Zoe Crosse, The leader and the key figure head of the Draco Syndicate, is a large and intimidating dragon of unknown age, origin and limit to her power.</description>
      <content>&lt;h1 id=&#34;uempress-zoe-crosseu&#34;&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Empress Zoe Crosse&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;images/zoepic.png&#34;  alt=&#34;Zoe Pic&#34;  class=&#34;left&#34;  style=&#34;float:right&#34;   width=&#34;500px&#34;   /&gt;


&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#about&#34;&gt;About&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#appearance&#34;&gt;Appearance&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#abilities&#34;&gt;Abilities&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#gear%20&amp;amp;%20weapons&#34;&gt;Gear &amp;amp; Weapons&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#relationships&#34;&gt;Relationships&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#reference%20images&#34;&gt;Reference Images&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#gallery&#34;&gt;Gallery&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#trivia&#34;&gt;Trivia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Catergories&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Details&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Nicknames&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Zo-Zo, Crimson Empress&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Species&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Dragon (Ancient Earth/Fire Dragon mix&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Age&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Adult (~27 physically, 1000+ actually)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Gender&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Trans-Female&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Pronouns&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;She/Her &amp;amp; They/Them&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Sexuality&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;AroAce&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;DOB&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;30th june&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Marital Status&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Single&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Place of Birth&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;???&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Residence&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Draco Syndicate Base, New Draconya&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Key abilities&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Antimatter manipulation, Conditional Immortality, Elemental Control, Mind control&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;about&#34;&gt;About:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoe Crosse, The leader and the key figure head of the Draco Syndicate, is a large and intimidating dragon of unknown age, origin and limit to her power. While she is fully capable of going to toe to toe with stellar entities and even some demi-gods, she mostly uses her powers to rule over the Draco Syndicate, a massive villainous network that spans over several different star systems&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;appearance&#34;&gt;Appearance:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoe is usually represented as a large, plus-sized black dragon, with shadings of dark grey for her wing membranes, her stomach, the under side of her tail and neck and in her large finned ears. Her head and her tail is adorned with a long, vibrant lipstick red hair, usually kept long and messy. Her body is also adorned with a pair of large wings, and a long and thick tail with a spiked end. On occasion, she takes on variations of her look, such as having three heads, a more snake-like lower body as opposed to her normal legs, and even at one point possessing a wolf-like body for a short time, however these forms are usually short live.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her usual, non-combative attire consists of a large black and red ball gown, with segmented sections on the main dress part of the gown, adorned with spikes, as well as a pair of black shoes with red soles and small spikes on the heel. Alongside this outfit, she also wears a pair of black bracelets and a black collar, adorned with spikes. While this dress is not used for combat, the gown&amp;rsquo;s segments are actually made of a symbiotic material, that one close to a chosen target can extend out to capture an unsuspecting person.
Her combat attire, while similar in design, features a base-line underlayer bodysuit that is similar in design to those worn by her drones, albeit adorned with the red and black that Zoe uses on a lot of her outfits, as well as lacking any form of explicit control devices e.g. Control collars, Control bracelets, Control insertion toys, as well as the visor being crimson red instead of the typical light rose colour that the normal drones have.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;character&#34;&gt;Character:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoe herself is quite the character; when she is in the presence of those other than her closest allies, she has a veneer of authority and power, with a bit of sass and spite thrown in for good measure. She is one that is know to strike fear into the hearts of weaker willed beings with just words. However, when she is around her closest allies, she allows herself to drop the veneer, revealing someone who genuinely cares about those who are close to her, as well as revealing a softer, kinder side that also resonates when she is around children and animals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;abilities--techniques&#34;&gt;Abilities &amp;amp; Techniques:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;abilities&#34;&gt;Abilities:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Due to a combination of factors, from the fact of being a dragon, and due to experimentations done on her by not only those who have captured her but by herself, Zoe has a wide array of different abilities at her disposal. The following is a list of notable powers and abilities that Zoe has at her disposal;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**Enhanced Physical Condition: ** Due to experimentation to her body, as well as decades of training, Zoe has perfected her body to a state where not only can she reach the limits of her body, but has surpassed them; From her physique, to her mental fortitude to even her reflexes have been fine tuned to far exceed that normally seen of a dragon. However, this physical state is nothing without the control and restraint to manage it, to which Zoe is very much capable of, being able to reduce her strength so that she doesn&amp;rsquo;t break people&amp;rsquo;s bodies from a single touch.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**Enhanced Mental Fortitude: ** While&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;gear--weapons&#34;&gt;Gear &amp;amp; Weapons:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;weapons&#34;&gt;Weapons:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;draco-sentinel-hammer&#34;&gt;Draco Sentinel Hammer:&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A large warhammer, forged out of pure draconic steel and augmented with similar nanites to those that comprise Zoe&amp;rsquo;s bodysuit, the Draco Sentinel hammer is a powerful warhammer that can deal large concussive blasts upon striking the ground, and can easily cover a target in drone goo with a single swing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;gear&#34;&gt;Gear:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;z-crosse--ancient-draconic-nano-symbiotic-battle-bodysuit&#34;&gt;Z-Crosse / Ancient Draconic Nano-symbiotic Battle Bodysuit:&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Originally an ancient battle bodysuit, used by the ancient dragons when piloting their gestalt armors, the Nano-Symbiotic Battle Bodysuit is a hybrid of ancient dragon technology, being augmented with Zoe&amp;rsquo;s modern technology into a hyper-advanced battlesuit that is sleek and moveable as the ancient battlesuits, with the adaptability and technical abilities from present nanosuits. The suit itself is capable of further augmenting Zoe&amp;rsquo;s natural abilities, enhancing her punches and her reflexes, as well as being able to patch wounds due to in-built medical stimulant injectors built into the nanites that comprise the suit. The suit also comes with retractable mask, with a full heads-up display for relaying information to Zoe in an instant, as well as a filtration mask that can block out toxins and even allow Zoe to breath in space with the usage of a rebreather. The suit, due to being comprised of nanites, is also able to shift into many different shapes, allowing for different configurations in an instant, such as manifesting back and feet thrusters to allow Zoe to fly at mach speeds, powerful arm blades to slash at opponents, or even an arm-mounted railgun for long ranged attacks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The original Ancient Draconic suit, which forms as the basis for this suit, had some of the features mentioned, namely the medical injectors and the helmet, however these were in a more rudimentary form. The main shape of the bodysuit, as well as the general material appearance of the bodysuit, is what inspired the look of the battle bodysuit that Zoe wears, and from this battlesuit came the base design for the Drones suits that all Z-Crosse Empire drones wear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;relationships&#34;&gt;Relationships&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;allies&#34;&gt;Allies:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;commander-opal-clover-nightstripe&#34;&gt;Commander Opal (Clover Nightstripe):&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Commander Opal, Also known by her real name of Clover Nightstripe, is one of the oldest and one of the highest ranked members of the Z-Crosse empire, even when compared to the other commanders. Commander Opal takes the form of a small feline girl, usually wearing a small ball gown-style dress, but in reality is far older, but is stuck in the younger body due to her old body being destroyed. Commander opal is the leader of the Opal divison, which has control over most of the drones. Clover is one of Zoe&amp;rsquo;s oldest friends, being one of the original researchers that studied Zoe, before becoming a member of the Z-Crosse Empire&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;commander-onyx-milo-stoneclaw&#34;&gt;Commander Onyx (Milo Stoneclaw):&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Commander Onyx, also known as Milo stoneclaw, is the second highest ranking member of the Z-crosse empire; Before joining the empire, Milo was a empovrished man, who had been shunned from his society due to his homosexuality. Zoe met milo when she first started her faction, and helped raise the man from squalor and into a life worth living. And, while she does not condone him doing such a thing, Milo has sworn his life to protect Zoe, to pay her back for saving him from squalor and bigotry. In trade, Commander Onxy controls the Onxy Sentinels, a division made of mostly sentinel-class drones and worker-class drones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;commander-cinnabar&#34;&gt;Commander Cinnabar&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;commander-sapphire&#34;&gt;Commander Sapphire&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;commander-jade&#34;&gt;Commander Jade&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;commander-obsidian&#34;&gt;Commander Obsidian&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;commander-apatite&#34;&gt;Commander Apatite:&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;reference-images&#34;&gt;Reference Images&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;STILL IN DEVELOPMENT&amp;lt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;gallery&#34;&gt;Gallery&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;STILL IN DEVELOPMENT&amp;lt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;trivia&#34;&gt;Trivia&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;authors-notes&#34;&gt;Author&amp;rsquo;s notes:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trace&#39;s Bio</title>
      <link>/characterbios/tracebio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 22:30:22 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/characterbios/tracebio/</guid>
      <description>trace wing is a honse, she goes nay (STILL IN DEVLEOPMENT)</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;trace wing is a honse, she goes nay
(STILL IN DEVLEOPMENT)&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technika&#39;s Bio</title>
      <link>/characterbios/technikabio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 22:30:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/characterbios/technikabio/</guid>
      <description>technika is a kirin, she go bork (STILL IN DEVLEOPMENT)</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;technika is a kirin, she go bork
(STILL IN DEVLEOPMENT)&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
